# **Jacob Dominguez**

I'm a Digital marketing student at Universidad de Palermo. I am courteous and enthusiastic, interested in computing, digital marketing and everything that is in its orbit. Specialized in front end development in interactive design in responsive websites.

Soler 5888
Buenos Aires, Argentina.
+54 911 25118442
jacobguillermooo@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Confidential**, Madrid, Spain — Web designer

2022 - PRESENT

Web page designer, in charge of front-end development using HTML, CSS, Javascript and React.js. For the landing page of the new brand.

## Mis Polleras, Panama — Community Manager

July 2020 - May, 2021

In charge of growing and segmenting the Instagram page, by creating content of the national costume of Panama (La Pollera). Using various technologies to improve the performance and benefits of the page.

### **Boulder54**, Panama — Waiter

January 2020 - March 2020

Assistant in all sectors of the restaurant, with a main focus on gala guests.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Hatfield Christian School**, Pretoria, Sudafrica — *High School* Bachelor's degree.

### **University of Palermo**, Buenos Aires, Argentina — *Student*

Current student in Management degree with a focus on digital business.

#### **PROJECTS**

## **Portfolio** — React.js

Display of my projects.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML

**CSS** 

JavaScript

React.js

**Bootstrap** 

Python

SQL

Canva

Microsoft Office.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Spanish - Native.

English - Advanced.